VIJAYAKUMAR ARIKATTI

Software Engineer

- 📞 6362363710 🔞 vijaykumararikatti@gmail.com 🕜 github.com/vijaykumararik 📝 linkedin.com/in/vijayakumar-arikatti
- Bangalore, Karnataka

EDUCATION

BE civil engineering

SDM college of engineering and technology dharwad,

GPA 9.38 / 10

= 08/2015 - 2019

• Dharwad

PUC PCMB

HIPU science college dharwad

Percentage **90.5** / 100

= 04/2013 - 03/2015

Oharwad

SSLC

Sri Maruti high school hirekerur,haveri

Percentage **80.1** / 100

= 2013 - 2013

Hirekerur

TECH STACK

Reactjs Redux Javascript

Html CSS Typescript

Mangodb Sql Java

Hibernate Springs Nodejs

LANGUAGES

TRAINING/COURSES

Java full-stack training
Jspiders Bangalore

SUMMARY

Front-end developer with 2+ years of experience building responsive web applications. I am proficient with HTML, CSS, JS, and Reactjs Frameworks, with good programming knowledge and logical implementation, and worked in real-time application development and understood the real-time requirements and scale of the project Woking in a team to achieve company goals and Completing tasks according to the requirements.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Nirvana Soft

\(\boxed{\omega} \) 04/2021 - 04/2023 \(\boxed{\omega} \) #13 Krishna Reddy Layout, Domlur, Bengaluru, Karnataka Nirvana Soft is committed to Corporate Training, Consulting and IT Services

- · Created a Hospital management system for the Health care,
- · Tech stack : Reactjs Redux, javascript, html, css, springboot, mysql database
- My role is to Code the Front end components using react js and implementing basic logic, and completing the tasks assigned by the team,
- · Understanding UI design and developing components.
- Helped me to gain sufficient knowledge to build real-world applications and understood the complete development process.

Mathematics subject matter expert

Class 21A Technologies Private Limited(Doutnut)

iii 03/2020 - 03/2021 ♀ Gurgaon, india

Class 21A Technologies Private Limited(Doutnut) is education platform where stsudents learn then subjects by video content.

- I had worked in the Content Development team as a Mathematics Subject Matter Expert and was actively and diligently involved in the projects and tasks assigned to me. And I worked as per the expectations of the company.
- I had the responsibility to ensure the content developed by experts was correct or not and to check it according to the requirements and guide experts about the corrections and mistakes made by them.

PROJECTS

Portfolio website using Reactjs

Developed a portfolio website containing all information

· tech stack:Reactjs,javascript,html,css,tailwind css.

Food Restaurant Website using reactjs

Developed modern food and restaurant website.

· tech stack:Reactjs,javascript,html,CSS

Basic Artificial Inteligence website design

Developed a basic Artificial intelligence website with an attractive design.

· tech stack:Reactjs ,javascript,html,css